One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
On your guard, everyone!
‫كونوا على أهبة الاستعداد جميعًا‬
– Yeah!
‫أجل‬
If those pirates get in with all of us on guard, it'll be an embarrassment to Galley-La!
‫إن سمحنا للقراصنة بالتسلل مع وجودنا جميعًا للحماية‬
Don't let them in!
‫لا تسمحوا لهم بالدخول أبدًا‬
What about the back door?
‫ماذا عن الباب الخلفي؟‬
Back door? We're surrounding the entire building!
‫الباب الخلفي؟ إنّنا نحاوط مبنى المكتب الرئيسي بأكمله‬
There are no blind spots!
‫لا توجد بقعة عمياء‬
Come get some! We'll take on your whole crew!
‫تعالوا إن أردتم، سنتخلص من طاقمكم بأكمله‬
– Yeah!
‫أجل‬
They're all armed and tough looking.
‫جميعهم يحملون الأسلحة ويبدون أقوياء‬
No surprise there. The shipwrights here can even beat pirates.
‫هذا طبيعي، فالسفانين هنا يستطيعون ردع حتّى القراصنة‬
We should be careful and act when the time is right.
‫علينا أن نحترس ونتحرك في التوقيت المناسب‬
Yeah, if we blindly charge in, it'll get real ugly for us.
‫أجل، ستحدث مصيبة إن اقتحمنا المكان دون حذر‬
That's rich coming from you!
‫من ذا الذي يقول هذا يا ترى؟ بعد أن قفز بلا خطة بعد الظهيرة‬
Chopper, we don't know what'll happen. Don't miss even the slightest movement.
‫،تشوبر، لا ندري ما سيحدث لا تفوّت أصغر التحركات‬
Okay.
‫نعم‬
Let us know immediately if anyone moves.
‫أعلمنا فورًا إن رأيت أيّ تحرك‬
Yep. Got it.
‫نعم، مفهوم‬
It'll be a long night, but don't let your guard down.
‫الليل طويل، ولكن لا تتهاون‬
If we miss our chance tonight, we'll be left with no idea of what happened.
‫إن ضيعنا الفرصة هذه الليلة‬
Just assume this is our last chance to go after Robin.
‫ضعوا في بالكم أنّنا لن نملك وسيلة للحاق روبين بعدها‬
Now's the time for us to step up.
‫علينا أن نبذل ما بوسعنا هنا‬
Yeah, we'll get Robin back no matter what.
‫أجل... سنمسك روبين حتمًا‬
Kalifa...
‫...كاليفا‬
Yes, Mr. Iceburg.
‫نعم يا أيسبرغ-سان‬
Sorry, but could you step outside for a moment?
‫آسف، ولكن أيمكنك الخروج قليلًا؟‬
Yes, sir.
‫مفهوم‬
Also...
‫...وأيضًا‬
please send Paulie in here.
‫استدعي باولي إلى هنا‬
Paulie...
‫...باولي‬
Mr. Iceburg has something important to tell you.
‫يقول أيسبرغ-سان أنّه يريد التحدث معك بأمر مهم‬
Me?
‫معي؟‬
Yes, just you.
‫نعم، أنت وحدك‬
I'll be in my office. Just call me if anything happens.
‫سأكون في مكتب السكرتارية لذا استدعني إن حدث أيّ شيء‬
Yeah...
‫...حسنًا‬
Of all the times to have a heart-to-heart...
‫لماذا يريد التحدث معك على انفراد في وقت كهذا؟‬
What the devil could it be about?
‫ما الأمر يا ترى؟‬
Beats me.
‫لا أدري‬
His last words?!
‫وصية؟‬
She said it was important. Get in there and talk to him already.
‫،قالت أنّه أمر مهم اذهب إليه بسرعة‬
Y-Yeah...
‫...أ-أجل‬
Shall we step away from the door for a bit?
‫هل من الأفضل أن نبتعد عن الباب قليلًا؟‬
I suppose so.
‫صحيح‬
I wonder what he needs to talk to Paulie about!
‫أتساءل ما الذي يريد التحدث مع باولي عنه‬
It's Mr. Iceburg we're talking about. It must be very important.
‫،إنّنا نتحدّث عن أيسبرغ-سان لا بدّ أنّه أمر مهم جدًّا‬
More importantly, we've got to deal with these pirates.
‫الأهم من ذلك، المشكلة الآن هي القراصنة‬
Yeah.
‫أجل‬
According to Kalifa's investigation, there are seven of them.
‫وفقًا لتحقيق كاليفا فهناك سبعة منهم‬
The captain, Straw Hat Luffy. Pirate Hunter Zoro and Nico Robin.
‫القبطان، قبعة القش لوفي ...صائد القراصنة زورو ونيكو روبين‬
There's also the girl who came to Dock One this afternoon and the lad with the rounded long nose.
‫علاوة على ذلك، الشابة التي أتت إلى الحوض الأول ظهيرة اليوم‬
Yeah. Aside from the ones mentioned, there are two others, and that's it.
‫أجل، يوجد اثنين غير هذين، سيكون هؤلاء جميعهم‬
Their goal is of no concern to us.
‫لا يهمنا هدفهم‬
Coming in here will be the last thing they ever do.
‫دخولهم إلى هنا سيكون نهايتهم‬
We'll put the whole crew down once and for all.
‫سنطيح بكامل طاقمهم  دفعة واحدة‬
– Yeah!
‫أجل‬
Okay... Understood.
‫حسنًا... مفهوم‬
This could be very risky.
‫سيكون هذا خطرًا جدًّا‬
I've been racking my brain, but you're the only one I can trust.
‫فكّرت به عميقًا، ولكن لا أستطيع طلب هذا من أحد غيرك‬
Will you do it for me?
‫هلّا فعلتها لي؟‬
You're acting like I'm a stranger. Please leave it to me.
‫،إنّك تعاملني كالغريب اترك الأمر لي‬
Thank you.
‫أعتمد عليك‬
Well then, I'll get on it immediately.
‫حسنًا إذًا، سأباشر حالًا‬
Please do.
‫أجل‬
Finished talking?
‫هل انتهيتما من الكلام؟‬
Yeah... Something came up.
‫نوعًا ما‬
It's okay. The four of us will be more than enough.
‫لا بأس، فأربعتنا نكفي‬
I see.
‫فهمت‬
Watch over Mr. Iceburg.
‫احرسوا أيسبرغ-سان‬
Listen, Paulie...
‫اسمع يا باولي‬
Right under the desk in my office...
‫...تحت طاولة مكتب الرئيس‬
lift up the carpet to find...
‫...إن رفعت السجادة، فستجد هناك‬
a safe buried there.
‫خزنة مدفونة‬
This must be it.
‫هذه هي‬
I'll give you the combination, so listen carefully.
‫سأعطيك رقمها، لذا استمع جيّدًا‬
First, right... six...
‫...أولًا، 6 إلى اليمين‬
Are you ready?
‫هل أنتما مستعدان؟‬
Yeah, we're ready.
‫نعم، مستعدان‬
Then I'll cause a disturbance.
‫سأتسبّب بالفوضى إذًا‬
The four of you will execute your assignments after the signal.
‫أرجو من أربعتكم أن تنفّذوا مهمّتكم بعد الإشارة‬
Roger.
‫...مفهوم‬
Ready, Nico Robin?
‫أمستعدة يا نيكو روبين؟‬
Yes... anytime.
‫نعم... في أيّ وقت‬
An explosion!
‫انفجار‬
What was that explosion just now?!
‫ما ذلك الانفجار؟‬
Bring water, now!
‫أحضروا الماء بسرعة‬
Take the injured someplace safe!
‫خذوا الجرحى إلى مكان آمن‬
Hurry! Put out the fire!
‫بسرعة، أطفؤوا النار‬
W-Was it cannon fire?
‫أ-أكانت هذه قذيفة مدفع؟‬
No, it didn't fly in!
‫لا، لم تطر من أيّ مكان‬
Somebody must've set it!
‫كانت مجهزة‬
Put out the fire! Hurry up and put out the fire!
‫أطفؤوا النار، أطفؤوا النار بسرعة‬
Someone, give me a hand!
‫فليساعدني أحدكم‬
That was one hell of a signal.
‫...يا لها من إشارة مبهرجة‬
Let's go!
‫لنذهب‬
The explosion was at the first floor's north corner.
‫حدث الانفجار في الزاوية الشمالية من الطابق الأول‬
Is everyone okay?!
‫هل جميعكم بخير؟‬
Half of you stay at your post! We still haven't seen the enemy!
‫،فليبق نصفكم على الأقل في أماكنهم لم نرَ العدو بعد‬
Fortify the perimeter and prepare for an attack!
‫حصّنوا الدفاعات للاستعداد للهجوم‬
Don't let them in the building!
‫لا تسمحوا لهم بالدخول إلى المبنى‬
Are you okay, Mr. Iceburg?!
‫هل أنت بخير يا أيسبرغ-سان؟‬
Yeah... I was surprised.
‫نعم... تفاجأت‬
I saw someone in the shadows!
‫رأيت شخصًا‬
She's wearing a costume! Catch her!
‫إنّه متنكّر، أمسكوا به‬
Here they come!
‫أتوا إذًا‬
Leave 'em to me!
‫اتركوهم لي‬
I'll get 'em!
‫سأنهيهم‬
Hey, wait!
‫أنتما، انتظرا‬
Good heavens...
‫...يا إلهي‬
This way! Catch her!
‫من هنا، أمسكوا به‬
Don't let her get away!
‫لا تدعوه يهرب مهما كلّف الأمر‬
She's all alone! Corner her!
‫إنّه وحده، حاصروه‬
Come on, pirate assassin!
‫تعال أيّها القرصان القاتل‬
She went upstairs using a whip!
‫صعد طابقًا باستخدام سوط‬
You thought there'd be no one on the rooftop?
‫اعتقدتَ أنّ لن يكون هناك أحد على السطح؟‬
Don't underestimate Galley-La's craftsmen.
‫لا تستخف بحرفيي غاليلا‬
How dare you mock us by attempting an assassination?!
‫كيف تجرؤ على القيام بأمور سخيفة مثل الاغتيال؟‬
Prepare yourself, pirate!
‫استعد أيّها القرصان‬
We're definitely not gonna forgive you bastards!
‫لن نغفر لكم أبدًا‬
Don't try anything. You're no match for me.
‫توقفوا، لا تستطيعون مجاراتي‬
There're two here!
‫يوجد اثنين هنا‬
They're headed to the back door!
‫إنّهما متوجهان صوب الباب الخلفي‬
Don't lose them! Attack from both sides! Don't let them inside!
‫،لا تسمحوا لهم بالهروب سنهاجمهم من الجانبين‬
Move! Capture them immediately!
‫الحقوهم، أمسكوا بهم حالًا‬
You memorized the layout of his residence, right, Nico Robin?
‫أحفظتِ مخططات قصره يا نيكو روبين؟‬
Yes.
‫نعم‬
Ahh... The craftsmen are in a frenzy.
‫الحرفيون مهتاجون‬
Yeah... It's pretty noisy down there.
‫أجل، أصبحت الأوضاع صاخبة‬
What do we do? We should probably get in there.
‫ماذا نفعل؟ هل نذهب؟‬
Hm? Where's Luffy?
‫لحظة، أين لوفي؟‬
– Think before you act!
‫فكّر جيّدًا قبل أن تتحرّك أيّها القبطان المغفل‬
Too late for that...
‫أأدركتما ذلك توًّا؟‬
The back door! They're headed to the back door! Corner them!
‫الباب الخلفي، توجها نحو الباب الخلفي، حاصروهما‬
Don't let them get away! Surround them!
‫لا تسمحا لهما بالهروب، حاصروهما‬
You got a death wish, showing your faces in front of all us guards?!
‫كيف تجرؤان على القدوم هكذا أمام كلّ هذا العدد من الحراس؟‬
Don't make light of the Galley-La craftsmen!
‫لا تستخفا بحرفيي غاليلا‬
Your fate was sealed the moment you laid a hand on Mr. Iceburg!
‫تقرّر مصيركم فور أذيّتكم لأيسبرغ-سان‬
Just give up!
‫استسلموا‬
You ain't going anywhere, pirates!
‫لن تستطيعا الهرب الآن أيّها القرصانان‬
Give up and show your faces!
‫استسلما واكشفا عن وجهيكما‬
You two will be bait for the rest of your crew, damn assassins!
‫سنستدرج باقي مجموعتكما باستغلالكما أيّها القتلة‬
He's gonna do something!
‫سيفعل شيئًا‬
Shoot them!
‫أطلقوا عليهما‬
They disappeared... No way!
‫اختفيا، مستحيل‬
What's going on?
‫ماذا يجري؟‬
Where'd they go?
‫إلى أين ذهبا؟‬
Hey, are you okay?
‫أنت، هل أنت بخير؟‬
She's strong... What's with that whip user?
‫إنّه قوي... ما خطب صاحب السوط ذاك؟‬
She ran... through the air.
‫ركض... في الهواء‬
No way...
‫...مستحيل‬
Ran through the air...?
‫ركض في الهواء؟‬
Seriously, you people never listen, do you?
‫يا إلهي، إنّكم لا تفهمون‬
She jumped off!
‫قفز‬
Moon Walk!
‫مشية القمر‬ ‫غيبو‬
There she goes again! She jumped while in midair!
‫ثانية، قفز في الفراغ‬
Briar Road!
‫الطريق الشائك‬ ‫إبارا رودو‬
I told you not to do that.
‫لذلك أخبرتكم أن تتوقفوا‬
Ah! She's coming!
‫ها قد أتى‬
She landed in the courtyard! Circle around behind her!
‫الفناء، هبط في الفناء، حاصروه‬
Hey! Over that way! Cut her off on both sides!
‫ذهب إلى هناك، اسبقوه وحاصروه من الجانبين‬
Okay!
‫حسنًا‬
This must be it.
‫لا بدّ أنّ هذه هي‬
Whoa...
‫...هكذا إذًا‬
So that's what Mr. Iceburg's been hiding, huh?
‫هذا ما كان يخفيه السيد أيسبرغ إذًا؟‬
Give it here.
‫سلّمنا إيّاه‬
You can't appreciate its value.
‫لا تستطيع تقدير قيمتها‬
Who the hell are you bastards?
‫من أنتما أيّها الوغدان؟‬
Where'd you come from?
‫من أين أتيتما؟‬
From the darkness.
‫الظلام‬
Even so, our group administers justice.
‫ولكنّنا مجموعة تنفّذ العدالة فحسب‬
We are Cipher Pol No. 9, a covert intelligence agency.
‫،نحن سايفر بول 9 جهاز استخبارات سري‬
Wherever you came from, you must've encountered our craftsmen.
‫من حيثما أتيتم‬
Did we?
‫لا أدري‬
We might have... or we might not have...
‫...ربما فعلنا... أو ربما لم نفعل‬
I don't really remember the details.
‫لا أتذكر التفاصيل جيّدًا‬
This is no longer a simple assassination, is it?
‫لم تعد هذه عملية اغتيال بسيطة‬
Well, I don't recall us calling it that.
‫لا نذكر تسميتنا لها بذلك‬
In any case, hand over Mr. Iceburg's valuable possession,
‫على أيّ حال، أعطنا هذا الغرض المهم الخاص بالسيّد أيسبرغ‬
and... since you've learned something about it...
‫...وأيضًا، بما أنّك عرفت شيئًا عن الأمر‬
you must die.
‫فنريدك أن تموت‬
In the name of justice...
‫...باسم العدالة‬
Right here... right now...
‫هنا والآن‬
Did you find the two who vanished near the back door?!
‫هل وجدتم الاثنان اللذان اختفيا عند الباب الخلفي؟‬
No! We can't find them anywhere!
‫لا، لم نجدهما في أيّ مكان‬
What about inside the residence?!
‫ماذا عن داخل القصر؟‬
There're guards at every window and door!
‫يتواجد الحرس عند كلّ نافذة وباب‬
No way they'd get in!
‫يستحيل أن يتسللوا‬
Damn pirates! Where'd they go?!
‫سحقًا لأولئك القراصنة، إلى أين ذهبوا؟‬
They've gotta be lurking nearby!
‫إنّهم يختبئون في مكان قريب بالتأكيد‬
Keep looking! Capture them no matter what! Got it?!
‫ابحثوا جيّدًا ثانية واحرصوا على القبض عليهم، أفهمتم؟‬
– Yeah!
‫نعم‬
He's behind this wall.
‫إنّه خلف هذا الحائط‬
Okay. Now, push me.
‫حسنًا، هيّا، ادفعيني‬
You startled me.
‫تفاجأت‬
I knew you'd come sooner or later...
‫...توقعت أن تأتوا عاجلًا أم آجلًا‬
but to think you'd come through there...
‫ولكن لم أتوقع من هنا‬
Did you do the same last night?
‫أقمتما بنفس الشيء البارحة؟‬
I know there isn't any door there.
‫لا يفترض أن يوجد باب هناك‬
It's the power of the Door-Door Fruit.
‫إنّها فاكهة الباب‬
No matter how hard a wall is, the area I touch becomes a door.
‫مهما كانت صلابة الحائط فإنّ المنطقة التي ألمسها تتحول إلى باب‬
As long as there's a wall, I can come and go as I please.
‫طالما يوجد حائط، فأستطيع الدخول والخروج من أيّ مكان‬
What was that?! We haven't got the signal yet.
‫ماذا تفعل؟ لم نتلقَ الإشارة بعد‬
He's not weakened enough if he's talking this much.
‫لا يمكن اعتبار الشخص مضعفًا حين يملك طاقة كافية للحديث‬
Any chef worth his salt wouldn't neglect to prepare ingredients ahead of time...
‫كما أنّ الطبّاخ الجيّد لن يغفل عن تجهيز المكونات مسبقًا‬
just as pros carefully restrain their target to prevent any unexpected actions before the appointed time.
‫على المحترفين أن يحذروا ويقيدوا ضحاياهم‬
So that's... CP9's way of doing things, huh?
‫هذا أسلوب السي بي 9 إذًا؟‬
You've read the situation well. You're exactly right.
‫تملك بصيرة جيّدة... بالضبط‬
I feel bad for how I treated Straw Hat...
‫...أسأت لقبعة القش‬
Seems he had nothing to do with this after all.
‫كما توقعت، لم يكن له علاقة بالأمر‬
You don't have to feel bad.
‫لا داعي للشعور بالأسف‬
You just told the truth that you saw me last night.
‫كلّ ما فعلتَه هو إدلاء حقيقة رؤيتك لي البارحة‬
That was also part of your plan?
‫كان ذلك جزءًا من خطتك أيضًا؟‬
That's right.
‫...صحيح‬
We kept you alive to pin the blame on the pirates.
‫أبقيناك حيًّا لنلفّق الجريمة على القراصنة‬
Besides, if we killed you suddenly...
‫وأيضًا، إن قتلناك فجأة‬
we wouldn't know where to find what we're after...
‫...فلن نعرف مكان ما نسعى خلفه‬
the blueprints of a certain ship.
‫مخطّط سفينة معينة‬
It's something secretly passed down from shipwright to apprentice for generations.
‫إنّه شيء متوارث سرًا‬
If you felt your life was in danger, then surely you'd entrust it to someone...
‫إن شعرتَ أنّ حياتك في خطر‬
And you chose Paulie, one of the Dock One foremen.
‫والرجل الذي اخترته هو باولي أحد كبار عمال الحوض الأوّل‬
Our agents are with him right now.
‫زملاؤنا معه الآن‬
So everything is going... exactly as you planned, right?
‫كلّ شيء يجري وفق خطتكم إذًا؟‬
Ensure everything remains flawless to the end.
‫احرصي على تأدية العمل بسلاسة حتّى النهاية‬
Okay.
‫أجل‬
I'll handle the shipwrights on the other side of the door.
‫سأذهب للتعامل مع السفانين خارج الباب‬
Nico Robin, finish him off.
‫أنهي هذا الرجل يا نيكو روبين‬
Once those two get the blueprints from Paulie, they'll contact you.
‫حالما يسلبان المخطّط من باولي، فسيتواصلان معك‬
Kill Iceburg at that moment.
‫اقتلي أيسبرغ حينها‬
Our mission is accomplished once we kill Paulie, who's come to know the truth.
‫تنتهي مهمتنا حالما نقتل باولي‬
After that, the Straw Hats will shoulder all the blame.
‫وستلفّق التهمة بالكامل على طاقم قبعة القش بعدها‬
Seriously, why can't he just listen to people's advice?!
‫يا إلهي... لماذا لا يستمع لنصائح الآخرين؟‬
It's always the same.
‫هذا المعتاد‬
But... Robin might be somewhere in that commotion, right?
‫ولكن... قد تكون روبين موجودة في خضم تلك الفوضى، أليس كذلك؟‬
What are we gonna do?! We have to be careful!
‫ماذا سنفعل؟ علينا أن نتحرك بحذر‬
But... depending on how you look at it, we've lucked out.
‫ولكن قد نكون محظوظين اعتمادًا على طريقة تفكيرنا بالأمر‬
When Luffy marches into enemy territory, does he take the side or back entrances?
‫حين يقتحم لوفي منطقة العدو‬
Not a chance.
‫مستحيل‬
I bet by now he's jumped or run headfirst into the residence,
‫لا بدّ أنّه اقتحم من الأمام الآن قافزًا أو راكضًا‬
happy just to be inside and running around aimlessly. Sound about right?
‫ويلاحقونه دون أن يعرف أين يذهب رغم أنّه دخل القصر، ألا تظنان ذلك؟‬
Yeah, sure does.
‫نعم، أظن ذلك‬
Yeah, definitely.
‫نعم، أظن‬
Right? The shipwrights all believe that Luffy is the ringleader of the group of culprits.
‫أليس كذلك؟ من وجهة نظر السفانون‬
Once the main event jumps in, everyone's attention is bound to be on him!
‫حالما يقتحم المكان، فسيجذب انتباه الجميع بالتأكيد‬
This means we can safely assume that the residence's front guard is lighter than usual!
‫بمعنى آخر، لا شكّ أنّ‬
So we'll easily cross the courtyard and slip into the crowd of rampaging shipwrights!
‫لذلك سنستغل تلك الفرصة‬
I see. So thanks to Luffy, right now's our best chance to get in, huh?
‫فهمت، نملك فرصة مثالية للاقتحام بفضل لوفي إذًا؟‬
I'm convinced! So, it should be okay to jump right in, huh?
‫هذا مقنع، سنكون بخير إن دخلنا إذًا؟‬
We can jump over that fence!
‫يبدو أنّنا نستطيع القفز فوق ذلك السياج‬
Let's do this! Ready?!
‫هل أنتما مستعدان؟‬
Okay, we're going in!
‫حسنًا، سندخل‬
Follow Luffy!
‫اتبعا لوفي‬
– How is this "lighter than usual"?!
‫أيّ حراسة خفيفة هذه؟‬
Dammit... I can't get out.
‫سحقًا... لا أستطيع الخروج‬
I wanted to jump into the building all fast and furious...
‫...أردت القفز إلى داخل المبنى وأنا مهتاج‬
but I'm stuck and can't move!
‫ولكنّي علقت ولا أستطيع الحراك‬
I'm stuck and can't move...
‫...لا أستطيع الخروج‬
I have to hurry...
‫...عليّ أن أسرع‬
Just wait, Robin!
‫انتظري يا روبين‬
What the hell is going on?!
‫ما هذا؟‬
Someone! Third floor!
‫أحد ما، الطابق الثالث‬
Come to the hall of the president's bedroom!
‫تعالوا إلى أمام غرفة الرئيس وغرفة النوم‬
The guards were wiped out! Someone! Come upstairs!
‫أُبيد الحرّاس، فليأتِ أحد‬
What are you saying?!
‫ماذا تعني؟‬
Tilestone!
‫تايلستون-سان‬
Kaku and Lucci should be there!
‫يفترض أن يكونا كاكو ولوتشي هناك‬
But they're...
‫...ولكن‬
Kaku! Lucci!
‫كاكو، لوتشي‬
Good grief, there's no end in sight. Still no word?
‫يا إلهي، لا نهاية لهذا، ألم يتصلا بعد؟‬
You bastard!
‫أيّها اللعين‬
How dare you!
‫كيف تجرؤ؟‬
What a noisy man.
‫رجل مزعج‬
Mr. Iceburg better be okay!
‫يستحسن أن يكون أيسبرغ-سان على ما يرام‬
Check on him yourself.
‫تحقّق بنفسك‬
Iron Body.
‫الجسد الحديدي‬ ‫تيكاي‬
His giant hammer...!
‫...مطرقته العملاقة‬
N-No way!
‫مـ-مستحيل‬
You son of a...
‫...أيّها‬
Let go, you bastard!
‫اتركني أيّها اللعين‬
Do you pride yourself on your brute strength?
‫أقوّتك الجبارة هذه هي فخرك؟‬
I can't move my arm! There's no way I can lose a contest of strength!
‫،لا أستطيع الحراك ...يستحيل أن يتفوق عليّ بالقوة‬
Three of the foremen have been...!
‫...ثلاثة من رؤساء العمال‬
Get reinforcements from below!
‫نادوا الدعم من الأسفل‬
Shave!
‫سورو‬ ‫انتقال آني‬
We found them!
‫وجدناهم‬
It's Roronoa Zoro!
‫إنّه رورونوا زورو‬
They finally showed up!
‫كشفوا أنفسهم أخيرًا‬
Don't let them get away!
‫لا تسمحوا لهم بالهروب‬
I saw her this afternoon too!
‫رأيت تلك المرأة بعد الظهيرة أيضًا‬
After them!
‫الحقوهم‬
Hey! Why isn't Luffy here?!
‫لماذا  لوفي غير موجود؟‬
How should I know?! I'd love to find out!
‫ما أدراني، هذا ما أريد سؤاله‬
What do we do?!
‫ما العمل؟‬
At this point, it's just like being caught in the act.
‫على أيّ حال، هذا أشبه بإمساكنا بالجرم المشهود‬
But going on the offensive will get us in!
‫سنجد طريقًا للدخول إن هاجمناهم‬
Wait, Zoro! What're you about to do?!
‫تمهّل يا زورو، ماذا ستفعل؟‬
Running around the building won't get us anywhere.
‫لن نستفيد شيئًا بالركض حول المبنى‬
We storm in through the front and find Robin.
‫سنقتحم المكان من الأمام ونبحث عن روبين‬
But they're shipwrights! They're not our enemy, you know!
‫ولكنّهم سفانون وليسوا أعداءنا‬
Don't worry. I'll use the backs of my swords!
‫لا تقلقا، سأستخدم ظهر سيوفي‬
Out of our way!
‫افتحوا الطريق‬
– You can still kill them like that!
‫ولكنّك تصيبهم بجروح مميتة‬
Well, this is a surprise.
‫حسنًا... تفاجأت‬
To be honest, I never thought I'd see you here... Nico Robin.
‫بصراحة، لم أظن أنّي سأقابلك هنا أبدًا يا نيكو روبين‬
Have we met before?
‫أتقابلنا من قبل؟‬
We met for the first time last night.
‫أوّل مرة كانت الليلة الماضية‬
But I've wanted to meet you... for a very long time.
‫ولكنّي لطالما أرد مقابلتك‬
I even put your wanted poster up in my room to ensure I never forgot.
‫حتّى أنّي وضعت ملصق طلبك للعدالة في غرفتي لأحرص ألّا أنسى أبدًا‬
Would you like an autograph?
‫هل تريد توقيعي؟‬
That would be...
‫سيكون ذلك... رائعًا‬
So you wanted to kill me?
‫أردت قتلي إذًا؟‬
That's right.
‫صحيح‬
Before you destroy the world!
‫قبل أن تدمري العالم‬
Why are you searching for the poneglyphs?!
‫لماذا تبحثين عن البونغليف؟‬
Since ancient times,
‫منذ قديم الزمان‬
the government has universally declared it a felony to seek out and decipher the poneglyphs.
‫أعلنت الحكومة عالميًا أنّ البحث عن البونغليف وفكّ رموزه‬
I'm sure you know that much.
‫يفترض أنّك تعرفين هذا‬
You, too, know of the existence of the poneglyphs.
‫أنت أيضًا تعرف بوجود البونغليف‬
Just knowing about it wouldn't be a crime.
‫المعرفة فحسب لا تعدّ جريمة‬
But... the only one in the whole world who can decipher those texts...
‫ولكن الشخص الوحيد الذي ...يستطيع فكّ رموز تلك النصوص‬
is you.
‫هو أنت‬
That's exactly why the government put such a huge bounty on your head,
‫ولهذا السبب وضعت الحكومة مكافأة على رأسك‬
even though you were only eight years old.
‫رغم أنّك كنت في الثامنة من عمرك فقط‬
It's because you're the only one in the world
‫هذا لأنّكِ الشخص الوحيد في العالم‬
who can restore the ancient weapon!
‫الذي يستطيع إعادة السلاح العتيق‬
I see... You know about the weapon.
‫هكذا إذًا... تعرف حتّى عن السلاح إذًا‬
All things considered... I never thought CP9 actually existed as an organization.
‫...ولكن‬
And if it exists,
‫بهذه الحالة، هذا يعني أنّك تركت قراصنة قبعة القش بالفعل‬
Odd behavior for a woman who's been on the run for twenty years, but...
‫من الغريب أن تتصرف امرأة تُلاحق منذ 20 عامًا هكذا‬
well, that's none of my concern.
‫ولكن حسنًا، لا علاقة لي بذلك‬
If deciphering the poneglyphs leads to the weapon's return,
‫إن اُستعيد السلاح عن طريق فكّ رموز البونغليف‬
the outcome will be the same
‫سواء كان حامله صالحًا أم شريرًا، فالنتيجة سيان‬
The weapon can never bring forth peace to this world.
‫يستحيل أن يجلب السلاح السلام للعالم‬
It will bring the end of the world.
‫سيتدمّر العالم بكل تأكيد‬
We mustn't call forth a relic of the past!
‫لا ينبغي لنا جلب مخلفات من الماضي‬
You're right. I agree with you.
‫صحيح، أوافقك‬
But it's also none of your business.
‫،ولكن لا علاقة لك بهذا مهما كان ما أفعله ببحثي في التاريخ‬
a stranger like you has no right to lecture me.
‫فأنت أيّها الغريب لا تملك حقًا لقول أيّ شيء لي‬
Well... I do have that right...
‫...حسنًا، ليس تمامًا‬
because in a sense, you and I are in the same boat.
‫بما أنّ حالي من حالك بأحد الأشكال‬
I possess...
‫...أنا‬
I possess the blueprints of the ancient weapon Pluton.
‫أملك مخطّطات السلاح العتيق بلوتون‬
The weapon's blueprints?!
‫مخطّطات السلاح؟‬
Pluton is the name of a battleship built on this island a long time ago.
‫بلوتون اسم سفينة حربيّة بُنيت في هذه الجزيرة قبل وقت طويل‬
The ancient engineer who created such a powerful weapon felt that
‫مهندس السفانة الذي صنع هذا السلاح القوي بشكل طاغي‬
if by chance Pluton were to ever run out of control, a counterforce would be needed to stop it.
‫شعر أنّه إن حدث وخرج بلوتون عن السيطرة‬
So, he handed down the blueprints to future generations.
‫ولهذا توارث المخططات لأجيال‬
The government...
‫...وللحصول عليها‬
has finally resorted to using force to acquire these blueprints.
‫لجأت الحكومة أخيرًا لاستعمال القوة‬
Imagine helping them without knowing any of that...
‫...إنّك تساعدينهم دون حتّى معرفة ذلك‬
I'm too shocked to speak.
‫أنا مصدوم لدرجة أنّي لا أستطيع التعليق‬
The man named Tom, who entrusted the blueprints with me,
‫الرجل الذي يدعى توم والذي ائتمن المخطّط عندي‬
was concerned about a girl who was the sole survivor of the Ohara incident twenty years ago.
‫كان قلقًا على فتاة‬
He said that although she was small,
‫قال أنّ: رغم صغرها‬
she was dangerous since she shared the ideology of the devils of Ohara.
‫إلّا أنّها خطيرة بما أنّها تملك فكر شعب أوهارا الشياطين‬
I inherited the creator's will, so I am responsible for stopping you!
‫وبما أنّي ورثت إرادة المخترع فأملك مسؤوليّة إيقافك‬
With the government now aware that the blueprints exist,
‫بما أنّ الحكومة عرفت عن وجود المخطّطات الآن‬
it would be better to just let them burn.
‫فكان من الأفضل لو حرقتهم من البداية‬
But as long as you're alive, I can't do that because the weapon may yet be restored!
‫ولكنّي لا أستطيع فعل ذلك لأنّك حيّة‬
Is that all you want to say before you die?
‫أهذا كل ما تريد قوله قبل أن تموت؟‬
With all due respect, even if you killed me and stopped its restoration,
‫مع كامل احترامي، إلّا أنّ حتّى وإن قتلتني وأوقفت استعادته‬
wouldn't allowing the blueprints to get stolen amount to the same thing?
‫فألن تكون النتيجة نفسها إن سُرقت المخطّطات منك؟‬
Well...
‫...حسنًا‬
let me tell you one more thing.
‫دعيني أخبرك شيئًا آخر‬
You're the ones who fell for my plan.
‫أنتم من وقع في الفخ‬
Oh, that's it!
‫هذه هي‬
I finally got out! That was terrible.
‫تمكنت من الخروج أخيرًا، كان ذلك فظيعًا‬
Alright, I'll swoop in for sure this time.
‫حسنًا، سأنقض عليهم هذه المرة بالتأكيد‬
Time to go capture Robin!
‫...سأذهب للإمساك بروبين‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬
Rocket!
‫الصاروخ‬ ‫روكيت‬
You're no match for our martial arts.
‫لست ندًّا لفنوننا القتاليّة‬
Now, hand it over already...
‫...هيّا، سلّمنا إيّاها بسرعة‬
or else it'll get stained with your blood.
‫وإلّا ستتلطخ بدمائك‬
Dammit...
‫...سحقًا‬
I thought... I could defeat you.
‫اعتقدتُ أنّي أستطيع الفوز عليكما‬
To tell you the truth...
‫...في الحقيقة‬
Mr. Iceburg told me to just run away.
‫أخبرني أيسبرغ-سان أن أهرب فورًا‬
He told me to drop it and run...
‫...أخبرني أن أتركها وأهرب‬
since...
‫...بما أنّها‬
it's a complete fake!
‫مزيّفة بالكامل‬
A fake, you said?
‫أتقول مزيّفة؟‬
How foolish...
‫...يا للحماقة‬
I don't know who you are, but this means your plan failed, doesn't it?
‫لا أعرف من تكونان، ولكن هذا يعني أنّ خطتكما فشلت، أليس كذلك؟‬
How pathetic. Sorry, pal.
‫مثير للشفقة، هذا مؤسف‬
I don't even know what you're looking for.
‫لا أعرف حتّى ما تبحثان عنه‬
How cocky... You think that you outwitted CP9?
‫يا للغطرسة... أتعتقد أنّك خدعت السي بي 9؟‬
In any case, you may only be a decoy,
‫على أيّ حال، رغم أنّك مجرد طُعم‬
but we can't let you live now that you're involved.
‫إلّا أنّنا لا نستطيع أن نبقيك حيًّا بما أنّك أصبحت متورطًا‬
I'm stuck! Dammit! I'm stuck again!
‫علقت، سحقًا، علقت ثانية‬
Why does this always happen?!
‫لمَ يحدث هذا دائمًا؟‬
Straw Hat...!
‫قبعة القش‬
Ah! The rope guy!
‫رجل الأحبال‬
What happened to you? Are you okay?
‫ما حلّ بك؟ هل أنت بخير؟‬
You're covered in blood. You sure are full of surprises!
‫،إنّك متلطخ بالدماء إنّك مليء بالمفاجآت‬
I should say the same about you! This is the third floor!
‫بل أنت كذلك، هذا الطابق الثالث‬
Straw Hat Luffy...
‫...قبعة القش لوفي‬
Did you come all this way to take the blame?
‫أتيت بنفسك لتُلبس بتهمة الجريمة؟‬
Ah! Masks!
‫أقنعة، أهذه أقنعة؟‬
Then you're the jerks who are using Robin! Give Robin back to us, you damn bastards!
‫لا بدّ أنّكم من يرغم روبين على القيام بالأشياء‬
Dammit! Hey! Say something!
‫سحقًا، أنتما، قولا شيئًا‬
Tempest Kick.
‫ساق العاصفة‬ ‫ران كوك‬
His kick sliced the wall!
‫قطعت ركلاته الحائط‬
Straw Hat!
‫قبعة القش‬
What the hell are these?
‫ما هذه؟‬
We've got an emergency situation.
‫لدينا حالة طارئة‬
We don't have time for you.
‫لا نملك الوقت للعبث معك‬
I can't move!
‫لا أستطيع التحرك‬
Hey, restrain that guy, too. We don't have time to fight them.
‫،أنت، قيّده أيضًا لا نملك الوقت للقتال‬
Right...
‫...نعم‬
It's me. Our plan hit a snag.
‫هذا أنا، حدثت مشكلة بخطتنا‬
Everyone, come to the bedroom immediately.
‫فليأتِ الجميع إلى غرفة النوم حالًا‬
Don't shoot Iceburg yet.
‫لا تطلقي النار على أيسبرغ بعد‬
Got that? Do not shoot Iceburg yet.
‫أفهمتِ؟ لا ينبغي لك أن تطلقي على أيسبرغ بعد‬
I wish I had more time to play with you, however...
‫...كنت أودّ مواجهتك أكثر قليلًا، ولكن‬
I'm terribly sorry, but something came up.
‫المعذرة، طرأ أمر ما‬
What?! Are you trying to run?!
‫ماذا، ستهرب؟‬
No.
‫لا‬
I'm needed elsewhere, so here's my finishing blow.
‫،بما أنّ لديّ أمر طارئ أعطيتك الضربة القاضية‬
Ah! Lulu's down!
‫...لولو-سان‬
With a single blow?!
‫بضربة واحدة؟‬
Hold it!
‫انتظر‬
She's flying again!
‫طار ثانية‬
Are you... okay?
‫هل أنت بخير؟‬
This is nothing!
‫هذا لا شيء‬
I see. Straw Hat, why did you come here?
‫فهمت، قبعة القش، لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟‬
Everyone thinks that you guys are the culprits.
‫يعتقد الجميع أنّكم الجناة‬
I'm sorry... This is all because we wrongly assumed your guilt.
‫آسف... كلّ هذا بسبب افتراضنا الخاطئ‬
Don't worry about it. We're used to being hunted.
‫لا بأس، فنحن معتادون على مطاردتنا‬
More importantly, a member of our crew was taken by masked men.
‫الأهم من ذلك، سُلب أحد أفراد طاقمنا من قِبل أولئك المقنعين‬
So I came to take her back.
‫لذلك أتيت لاستعادتها‬
Nico Robin, right?
‫تتحدّث عن نيكو روبين، أليس كذلك؟‬
You seem like a strong fighter.
‫أنت قويّ بالقتال، أليس كذلك؟‬
Yeah, I am!
‫نعم، أنا كذلك‬
Can you beat them?
‫أتستطيع هزيمتهم؟‬
Yes, I can!
‫أستطيع‬
Then, fight with me! I wanna beat them, too!
‫قاتل معي أيضًا، أريد هزيمتهم‬
You do...
‫...هكذا إذًا‬
Of course I do!
‫بالطبع‬
Why... Why does Mr. Iceburg have to die at the hands of some idiot freaks?
‫لماذا... لماذا على أيسبرغ-سان أن يُقتل على يد غرباء حمقى؟‬
Give me a break! Who the hell are those people?!
‫لا تعبثوا معي، ما خطبهم؟‬
To hell with these secret agent bastards!
‫ماذا تعنون بجهاز استخبارات سري أيّها الأوغاد؟‬
That man... He's my mentor.
‫إنّه... معلمي‬
He helped me become a master shipwright!
‫ساعدني لأصبح سفّان ممتاز‬
Why do this to someone like him?!
‫...لماذا شخص مثله قد‬
You're in no shape to...
‫...ولكن كيف بإصاباتك هذه‬
I said I want to beat the crap out of those idiots!
‫قلت أنّي أريد أن أبرح أولئك الأوغاد ضربًا‬
Who cares what happens to my body after that?!
‫لا يهمني ما يحدث لجسدي لاحقًا‬
I'll fight till I'm nothing but bones!
‫سأقاتل حتّى آخر جزء من عظامي‬
Dammit! Take these off!
‫سحقًا، أزيلوها‬
Okay! Take them off! Dammit!
‫حسنًا، أزيلوها، سحقًا‬
Go home!
‫عودوا‬
I've got nothing to give you!
‫لا أملك شيئًا أعطيكم إيّاه‬
That puts us in quite a bind.
‫إلّم تملكه، فهذه مشكلة‬
Where should I begin...
‫...ماذا عليّ أن أخبرك أوّلًا‬
as you face death?
‫حيث أنّك تكاد أن تموت؟‬
You've disappointed me.
‫خاب أملي فيك‬
Lucci!
‫لوتشي‬
It's your own fault.
‫إنّه خطؤك‬
You should've handed them over to the government when they asked nicely.
‫كان ينبغي أن تسلمه للحكومة بعد أن طلبوا بلطف‬
Kaku!
‫كاكو‬
I wish my memories of this city could have been free of hurting you.
‫لو كان ذلك ممكنًا، أردت جعل هذه المدينة جزءًا من ذكرياتي دون أذيتك‬
Kalifa...
‫...كاليفا‬
So you also inherited your master's obstinacy, huh?
‫ورثت عناد معلّمك إذًا؟‬
Blueno, from the bar...
‫...بلونو من الحانة‬
You guys... work for... the government?
‫أنتم... تعملون لمصلحة الحكومة؟‬
That's right.
‫صحيح، التخفي كان مهمة سهلة بالنسبة لنا‬
Going undercover was a pretty easy mission for us.
‫سايفر بول 9 وكالة الاستخبارات السرية تحت إمرة حكومة العالم‬
I must say, your shrewdness leaves me at a loss for words.
‫ولكن حنكتك أبهرتني‬
Now, Mr. Iceburg...
‫...حسنًا يا أيسبرغ-سان‬
Where are the blueprints for the ancient weapon Pluton?
‫أين مخطّطات السلاح القديم بلوتون؟‬
Unless you want more people to get hurt, please tell us what we want to know.
‫أرجوك أخبرنا قبل أن يتأذّى الكثير من الناس‬